A Guide to the Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - George Rogers Clark Papers, 1776-1795, 1834-1835
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - George Rogers Clark Papers, 1776-1795, 1834-1835
The Library of Virginia
APA 204
21.1 cu. ft. (33 boxes) and 25 volumes
Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Auditor of Public Accounts in 1913.
Alternative Form Available
Please use the microfilm [Misc. Reels 3349-3361] or the photostat volumes in lieu of the originals.
Biographical Information
George Rogers Clark was born 19 November 1752 in Albemarle County, Virginia, to John Clark (1725-1799) and Ann Rogers Clark (1728-1798). Clark learned surveying from his grandfather in Caroline County, Virginia. He explored down the Ohio and Kanawha Rivers in what is now Kentucky and West Virginia and surveyed farms for settlers arriving in that territory. Clark served as a captain in the Virginia militia during Lord Dunmore's War in 1774, and the next year returned to Kentucky to survey lands for the Ohio Company. When the Revolution began, Clark encouraged Virginia to protect Kentucky from the British and indians. He captured Kaskaskia, Illinois, from the British 4 July 1778 and won the allegience of French settlers in Vincennes, Indiana. When the British took Vincennes in October 1778, Clark recaptured it 25 February 1779. He was responsible for the defense of the Northwest Territory during the rest of the American Revolution. After Kentucky troops were defeated at Blue Licks, Kentucky, by the Shawnee 19 August 1782, Clark retaliated with an attack on Chillicothe, Ohio, defeating the Shawnee 4 November 1782. After the American Revolution ended, Clark served on the Board of Commissioners which allotted the lands in Kentucky and the Northwest Territory granted by Virginia to its soldiers. Clark lived the last few years of his life with his sister and her husband outside Louisville, Kentucky, where he died 13 February 1818.
Scope and Content
This is an artificial collection of records concerning George Rogers Clark and the conquest of the Old Northwest during and after the revolutionary war. The records, which are now so intermingled they defy any attempt to separate them, were brought together from two distinct sets of records. The first set contained Clark's original accounts and vouchers, which had been submitted to the auditors of public accounts for settlement in 1779. These records were misplaced by the auditors and when the Board of Western Commissioners sought to settle his accounts in 1783, Clark produced a second set of records consisting of copies of the materials submitted in 1779, in addition to the records he had created since then. The Clark papers, then, consist of the misplaced records (since found) submitted to the auditor, as well as the vouchers submitted to the Board of Western Commissioners.
Papers, 1776-1795 and 1834-1835, including correspondence - some military in nature and the remainder concerning George Rogers Clark's accounts - as well as the accounts and vouchers submitted for settlement in 1779 and 1783. The accounts contain the names of persons to whome payments were made, the amounts, and the dates paid. The vouchers include the names of persons to whom money was owed, the amounts and dates the vouchers were submitted.
Some of the material that had long been part of the Clark records was separated from it in 1975 and interfiled with the Office of the Governor records, in the Letters Received series [available online at: Governor's Letters Received, 1776-1784, Database]. The records removed consisted mostly of correspondence with the governor and Council of State. In lieu of the original documents photocopies or tracers (handwritten notes that included the date and author of letter) were left in the Clark papers. In 2018 the archivist made copies of all of the separated letters to replace the tracers. Some of the letters had been reprinted in part or whole in the "Calendar of Virginia state papers: and other manuscripts preserved in the Capitol at Richmond." Noted on the tracers were the volume and page numbers where the letter had been reprinted. For example a handwritten notation, 'printed 3C 278', refers to Volume 3 and page 278, of the Calendar.
The Society of Colonial Wars in the State of Illinois and the Sons of the Revolution in the State of Illinois funded a microfilming and indexing project of the George Rogers Clark Papers at the Library of Virginia. The index is available online here: George Rogers Clark Papers Index. Not only does the website index the papers, but it also includes descriptions of each item in the collection, as well as the date and names.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Papers, 1776-1795, 1834-1835
Series II: Photostat volumes, 1776-1795
Contents List
- Series I: Papers, 1776-1795, 1834-1835., Extent: 14.85 cu. ft. (33 boxes). (Box 1-)
  Papers, 1776-1795 and 1834-1835, including correspondence - some military in nature and the remainder concerning George Rogers Clark's accounts - as well as the accounts and vouchers submitted for settlement in 1779 and 1783. The accounts contain the names of persons to whome payments were made, the amounts, and the dates paid. The vouchers include the names of persons to whom money was owed, the amounts and dates the vouchers were submitted.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1776-1777 [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1778 January [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1778 March [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1778 April [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1778 May [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1778 June [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1778 August [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1778 September [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1778 October [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1778 November [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1778 December [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1779 January [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1779 February [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1779 March 1 - 8 [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1779 March 9 - 16 [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1779 March 17 - 23 [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1779 March 24 -31 [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1779 April 1 - 5 [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1779 April 6 - 10 [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1779 April 11 - 18 [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1779 April 19 - 30 [Misc. reel 3349] (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1779 May 1 - 9 [Misc. reel 3349-3350] (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1779 May 10 - 19 [Misc. reel 3349-3350] (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1779 May 20 - 26 [Misc. reel 3349-3350] (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1779 May 27 - 31 [Misc. reel 3349-3350] (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1779 June 1 - 7 [Misc. reel 3350] (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1779 June 8 - 13 [Misc. reel 3350] (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1779 June 14 - 20 [Misc. reel 3350] (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1779 June 21 - 23 [Misc. reel 3350] (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1779 June 24 - 26 [Misc. reel 3350] (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1779 June 27 - 30 [Misc. reel 3350] (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1779 July 1 - 9 [Misc. reel 3350] (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1779 July 10 - 14 [Misc. reel 3350] (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1779 July 15 - 20 [Misc. reel 3350] (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1779 July 21 - 25 [Misc. reel 3350] (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1779 July 26 - 31 [Misc. reel 3350] (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1779 August 1 - 9 [Misc. reel 3350-3351] (Box 4, Folder 5 - 6)
  - 1779 August 10 - 19 [Misc. reel 3350-3351] (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - 1779 August 20 - 31 [Misc. reel 3350-3351] (Box 5, Folder 3 - 4)
  - 1779 September 1 - 9 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1779 September 10 - 19 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1779 September 20 - 30 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1779 October 1 - 9 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1779 October 10 - 19 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1779 October 20 - 31 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1779 November 1 - 9 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1779 November 10 - 19 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1779 November 20 - 30 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1779 December 1 - 9 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1779 December 10 - 19 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1779 December 20 - 31 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1779, Miscellaneous [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1780 January 1 - 15 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1780 January 16 - 31 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1780 February 1 - 14 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1780 February 15 - 29 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1780 March 1 - 15 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1780 March 16 - 31 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
  - 1780 April 1 - 15 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1780 April 16 - 30 [Misc. reel 3351] (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1780 May 1 - 16 [Misc. reel 3352] (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1780 May 17 - 31 [Misc. reel 3352] (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1780 June 1 - 15 [Misc. reel 3352] (Box 8, Folder 5 - 6)
  - 1780 June 16 - 30 [Misc. reel 3352] (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1780 July 1 - 15 [Misc. reel 3352] (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
  - 1780 July 16-31 [Misc. reel 3352] (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
  - 1780 August 1 - 15 [Misc. reel 3352] (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1780 August 16 - 31 [Misc. reel 3352] (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1780 September [Misc. reel 3352] (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
  - 1780 October [Misc. reel 3352] (Box 10, Folder 5-7)
  - 1780 November [Misc. reel 3352-3353] (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1780 December, Letters [Misc. reel 3353] (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1780 December [Misc. reel 3353] (Box 11, Folder 3-5)
  - 1780 Miscellaneous [Misc. reel 3353] (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1781 January, Letters [Misc. reel 3353] (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1781 January, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3353] (Box 12, Folder 2-5)
  - 1781 February, Letters [Misc. reel 3353] (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1781 February, Accounts [Misc. reel 3353] (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 1781 February, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3353] (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
  - 1781 February, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3353] (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - 1781 March, Letters [Misc. reel 3354] (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 1781 March, Receipts [Misc. reel 3354] (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 1781 March, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3353] (Box 13, Folder 5-9)
  - 1781 April, Letters [Misc. reel 3354] (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 1781 April, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3354] (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
  - 1781 May, Letters [Misc. reel 3354] (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 1781 May [Misc. reel 3354] (Box 14, Folder 6-8)
  - 1781 May [Misc. reel 3354] (Box 15, Folder 1-3)
  - 1781 June, Letters [Misc. reel 3354] (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 1781 June, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3354] (Box 15, Folder 5-9)
  - 1781 June, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3354] (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 1781 July, Letters [Misc. reel 3354] (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 1781 July, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3355] (Box 16, Folder 3-8)
  - 1781 August, Letters [Misc. reel 3355] (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 1781 August, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3355] (Box 17, Folder 2-6)
  - 1781 September, Letters [Misc. reel 3355] (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 1781 September, Accounts [Misc. reel 3355] (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 1781 September, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3355] (Box 18, Folder 3-6)
  - 1781 September, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3356] (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
  - 1781 October, Letters [Misc. reel 3356] (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 1781 October, Accounts [Misc. reel 3356] (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 1781 October, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3356] (Box 19, Folder 3-5)
  - 1781 November, Letters [Misc. reel 3356] (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 1781 November, Accounts [Misc. reel 3356] (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - 1781 November, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3356] (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - 1781 December, Letters [Misc. reel 3356] (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 1781 December, Accounts [Misc. reel 3356] (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - 1781 December, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3356] (Box 20, Folder 3-5)
  - 1781 Miscellaneous, Accounts [Misc. reel 3356] (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - 1781 Miscellaneous [Misc. reel] (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
  - 1781 - 1782 [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - 1782 January, Letters [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 1782 January, Accounts [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 1782 January, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
  - 1782 February, Letters [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 1782 February, Accounts [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - 1782 February, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
  - 1782 March, Letters [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - 1782 March, Accounts [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - 1782 March, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - 1782 April, Letters [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 1782 April, Accounts [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 1782 April, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 22, Folder 3-5)
  - 1782 May, Letters [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 1782 May, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
  - 1782 June, Letters [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 1782 June, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 23, Folder 2-5)
  - 1782 July, Letters [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - 1782 July, Accounts [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - 1782 July, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3357] (Box 24, Folder 1-4)
  - 1782 August, Letters [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 1782 August, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 24, Folder 6-7)
  - 1782 September, Letters [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - 1782 September, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 1782 October, Letters [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - 1782 October, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
  - 1782 November, Letters [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - 1782 November, Accounts [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - 1782 November, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - 1782 December, Letters [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - 1783 January, Letters [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - 1783 January, Vouchers[Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 1783 January, Misc. [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 1783 February, Letters [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 1783 February, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - 1783 March, Letters [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 1783 March, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - 1783 April, Letters [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - 1783 April, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - 1783 May, Letters [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - 1783 May, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - 1783 June, Letters [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - 1783 June, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - 1783 July, Letters [Misc. reel 3358] (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - 1783 July, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3358-3359] (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - 1783 August, Letters [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - 1783 August, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - 1783 September, Letters [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 1783 September, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 1783 October, Letters [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - 1783 October, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - 1783 November, Letters [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - 1783 November, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - 1783 December, Letters [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - 1783 December, Accounts [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - 1783 December, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 27, Folder 11-12)
  - 1782, Misc. [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - 1782-1783, Misc. [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - 1783 January [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - 1784 February [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
  - 1784 March [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - 1784 April [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - 1784 May [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - 1784 June, Letters [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - 1784 June [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - 1784 July, Letters [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - 1784 August, Letters [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - 1784 August, Daniel Boone, etc. [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - 1784 August, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 28, Folder 12-13)
  - 1784 August, Vouchers [Misc. reel 3359] (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - 1784 September [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 2-4)
  - 1784 October-November [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - 1784 December [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - 1785 January [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - 1785 February [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - 1785 March [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - 1785 April [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - 1785 May [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - 1785 June [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - 1785 July [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - 1785 August [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - 1785 September [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - 1785 October-November [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - 1785 December [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - 1786 January-August, Letters [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - 1786 September-December, Letters [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - 1786 Vouchers [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - 1787 January-June [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - 1787 July-December [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - 1788 [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - 1789 [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - 1790 [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - 1791 [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - 1792 [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - 1793 [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - 1794 [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - 1795 [Misc. reel 3360] (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - 1834, Illinois claims adjusted [Misc. reel 3361] (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - 1835, Illinois regiment claims filed by Sidney Breese [Misc. reel 3361] (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Undated [Misc. reel 3360-3361] (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
  - Wrappers and miscellaneous (Box 32)
  - Oversize, 1776-1779 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Oversize, 1779 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Oversize, 1779-1780 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Oversize, 1780-1781 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Oversize, 1781 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Oversize, 1781 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Oversize, 1781 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Oversize, 1781-1782 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Oversize, 1783-1785 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Oversize, 1785 and undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Series II: Photostat volumes, 1776-1795., Extent: 6.25 cu. ft. (25 volumes). (Volume 1-25)
  The Photostat volumes series consists of 25 positive photostat volumes of items duplicated by the R.C. Ballard Thurston Collection at the Filson Historical Society (Louisville, Ky.). The volumes have been arranged by the Society in the followlng groups: Series A-H - Orders on Commissaries, letters, accounts, etc.; Series I - Commissioners reports; Series J - Petitions and other papers; Series K - Muster rolls; Series L - Accounts, letters, etc.; Series M - Endorsements; Series N - Bounty warrants; Series O - Commissioners reports - Rejected claims and Series P - Miscellaneous.
  The names of many of the soldiers recorded in the volumes are indexed in John H. Gwathmey's, Historical Register of Virginians in the Revolution (Richmond: The Dietz Press, 1938).
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Photostat volume, Series A, Volume 1 [pages 1-295]
  - Photostat volume, Series A, Volume 2 [pages 296-628]
  - Photostat volume, Series A, Volume 3 [pages 629-1000]
  - Photostat volume, Series B, Volume 1 [pages 1-320]
  - Photostat volume, Series B, Volume 2 [pages 321-655]
  - Photostat volume, Series B, Volume 3 [pages 656-1000]
  - Photostat volume, Series C, Volume 1 [pages 1-500]
  - Photostat volume, Series C, Volume 2 [pages 501-1000]
  - Photostat volume, Series D, Volume 1 [pages 1-500]
  - Photostat volume, Series D, Volume 2 [pages 501-1000]
  - Photostat volume, Series E, Volume 1 [pages 1-500]
  - Photostat volume, Series E, Volume 2 [pages 501-1000]
  - Photostat volume, Series F, Volume 1 [pages 1-500]
  - Photostat volume, Series F, Volume 2 [pages 501-1000]
  - Photostat volume, Series G, Volume 1 [pages 1-500]
  - Photostat volume, Series G, Volume 2 [pages 501-1000]
  - Photostat volume, Series H, Volume 1 [pages 1-360]
  - Photostat volume, Series H, Volume 2 [pages 361-718]
  - Photostat volume, Series L, Volume 1 [pages 1-115]
  - Photostat volume, Series M, Volume 1 [pages 1-296]
  - Photostat volume, Series M, Volume 2 [pages 297-592]
  - Photostat volume, Series O, Volume 1 [pages 681-840]
  - Photostat volume, Miscellaneous, Volume 1 [page 1-369]
  - Photostat volume, Miscellaneous, Volume 2 [pages 370-600]
  - Photostat volume, Miscellaneous [Series P], Volume 3 [pages 601-778]